Finding Aid for Wilber M. Brucker Papers 1877-1968
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Subject files, 1908-1966
  - Wayne County Republican Convention, 1941; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Wayne County Republican Convention, 1942 (Box 14)
  - Republican party, 1942-1944; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - War effort, 1941-1943 (Box 14)
  - Republican party, 1944-1946 (Box 14)
  - Wilber Brucker Portrait Fund, 1946-1952; 5 folders (Box 14)
  - Political campaign, 1946; 4 folders (Box 14)
  - Fourteenth Congressional District, 1946-1952 (Box 14)
  - Primary election, 1947 (Box 15)
  - Re election, 1947 (Box 15)
  - General, 1947 (Box 15)
  - One-man grand jury, 1947-1951; 9 folders (Box 15)
  - Taft-Hartley Act, 1947 (Box 15)
  - Michigan legislature, 1947 (Box 15)
  - Republican party, 1947 (Box 15)
  - Republican Convention, 1948; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Republican State Convention, 1948 (Box 15)
  - Election, 1948; 5 folders (Box 15)
  - Brucker vs. Black slander case, 1947-1954; 12 folders (Box 15)
  - Michigan Revenue Department hearing on Harry Galperin, 1948; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - General, 1948; 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Republican State Convention, 1949 (Box 15)
  - Republican party, 1949; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Michigan legislature, 1949 (Box 16)
  - General, 1949 (Box 16)
  - Republican party, 1950, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - General, 1950 (Box 16)
  - Republican party, 1951 (Box 16)
  - General, 1951 (Box 16)
  - Republican party, 1952 (Box 16)
  - Saginaw High School Distinguished Alumnus Program, 1952 (Box 16)
  - Teamster Voting Fraud at Crawford Door Company, 1953 (Box 16)
  - General, 1953 (Box 16)
  - Republican party, 1953 (Box 16)
  - Invitations and programs, 1954 (Box 16)
  - Republican party, 1954; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Eightieth Birthday Celebration of Herbert Hoover, 1954 (Box 16)
  - General, 1954 (Box 16)
  - Republican party, 1955; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - "Background material on Security" for Secretary of the Army, 1955 (Box 16)
  - Briefing for "Meet the Press" appearance, 1955; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - European trip, 1955 (Box 16)
  - General, 1955 (Box 16)
  - Republican convention, 1956 (Box 16)
  - Republican Campaign, 1956 (Box 16)
  - Republican campaign, 1956; 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Republican campaign press releases, 1956 (Box 17)
  - Statement on Air Force Missile Bases, 1956 (Box 17)
  - General, 1956 (Box 17)
  - Memos on Little Rock, Arkansas incident, 1957 (Box 17)
  - Republican party literature, 1957 (Box 17)
  - Michigan Republican party, 1957 (Box 17)
  - Presidential inaugural, 1957 (Box 17)
  - General, 1957 (Box 17)
  - Republican party literature, 1958; 4 folders (Box 17)
  - Complaints of Neil Staebler re. Army certificate given to Charles Porter, 1958 (Box 17)
  - Secretary of the Army miscellaneous (Box 17)
  - Tour of Saint Lawrence Seaway, 1958 (Box 17)
  - Grimshaw vs. Aske et al., corruption case, 1958 (Box 17)
  - Michigan Republican party, 1958 (Box 17)
  - General, 1958 (Box 17)
  - Republican party, 1959; 3 folders (Box 17)
  - General, 1959 (Box 17)
  - Republican party, 1960; 5 folders (Box 17)
  - National Defense literature, 1960 (Box 17)
  - "Task Force Report: American Strategy and Strength", 1960 (Box 17)
  - General, 1960 (Box 17)
  - Republican National Committee literature, 1960 (Box 17)
  - Clark, Klein, Brucker and Waples Law Firm, 1937-1961; 11 folders (Box 17)
  - Michigan Republican party, 1961 (Box 18)
  - Welcome Home reception, 1961 (Box 18)
  - General, 1961 (Box 18)
  - Michigan Republican party literature, 1962 (Box 18)
  - Fourteenth Congressional District and elections, 1962 (Box 18)
  - Fourteenth Congressional District and gubernatorial campaign of George Romney, 1962; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Dinner for General William Westmore, 1962 (Box 18)
  - General, 1962 (Box 18)
  - Inauguration of George Romney, 1963 (Box 18)
  - U.S. Army miscellanea, 1963 (Box 18)
  - Richard Durant vs. John A. Stahlin et al.
    [libel suit concerning politics in Fourteenth Congressional District]
    - 1963, 11 folders (Box 18)
    - 1964, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - 1965, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Undated (Box 18)
    - Clippings (Box 18)
  - United Presbyterian Men, 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Republican party literature, 1964 (Box 18)
  - Republican party convention, 1964 (Box 18)
  - Election, 1964 (Box 18)
  - Fourteenth Congressional District, 1964 (Box 18)
  - Republican party, 1964 (Box 18)
  - General, 1964 (Box 18)
  - Republican party, 1965 (Box 18)
  - General, 1965 (Box 18)
  - Legislative Reapportionment, 1963-1966
    - Petition of Ivan Brown, February 3, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Petition of Henry J. Donguillo, February 7, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Petition of Richard H. Austin and Robert Kleiner, February 14, 1964; 4 folders (Box 19)
    - Petition of Wilber Brucker, et al., February 14, 1964; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Objections of Richard Austin and Robert Kleiner to plan of Brucker et al., February 21, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Statement concerning proposed apportionment plan: Ivan Brown, February 15, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Written objections of Wilber Brucker, February 24, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Petition of Richard Austin and Robert Kleiner for leave to file alternate districting and apportionment plan, May 11, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Petition of Austin, et al. for designation of plan to apportion and designate Michigan legislature, June 20, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Court hearings, 1963-1966; 11 folders (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1966; 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Commission on Legislative Apportionment
      - Rules, Budget, Procedures, 1963 (Box 19)
      - Press Releases, 1963 (Box 19)
      - Committee Meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 19)
      - Committee Meetings, 1965 (Box 19)
      - Brochures, 1964 (Box 19)
      - Plans, maps, and population figures, 1963-1964; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea, 1963-1964 (Box 19)
      - Senate Plans, 1965; 3 folders (Box 20)
      - House Plans, 1965; 4 folders (Box 20)
      - Votes on Plans, December 1965 (Box 20)
      - Statements to Commission, November-December, 1965 (Box 20)
      - Detroit Reapportionment Plans, 1963-1964; 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Notebooks, 1963-1964; 2 volumes (Box 20)
      - Miscellanea, 1964-1966; 3 folders (Box 20)
  - General, 1966 (Box 21)
  - Republican State Committee, 1967 (Box 21)
  - Herbert Hoover Birthplace and Institution on War, Peace and Revolution, 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - General, 1967 (Box 21)
  - General, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Economic Club of Detroit First Federal Savings and Loan Association, Detroit, 1968 (Box 21)
  - General, 1954-1956 (Box 21)
  - General, 1957-1960 (Box 21)
  - General, 1961-1968 (Box 21)
  - Saginaw (Mich.) High School reunion material
    - 1939 (Box 21)
    - 1946-1954 (Box 21)
    - 1952, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - 1962, 4 folders (Box 21)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 21)
  - University of Michigan Law School Reunion Material
    - 1941-1956 (Box 21)
    - 1961-1966 (Box 21)
  - Miscellanea, 1949-1951 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous campaign materials (Box 21)
  - Miscellanea (Box 21)
  - Papers concerning death of Wilber Brucker (Box 21)
- Knights Templar
  Brucker was a loyal Mason (Knights Templar). From his years as eminent grand master of the Grand Encampment of the Knights Templar of the United States, 1964-67, Brucker preserved much of the correspondence and memorabilia relating to the charitable activities of the Masons.
  - Trinity Youth Center, Detroit, 1955 (Box 22)
  - Thirteenth Annual Easter Sunrise Service, Arlington Cemetery, Washington, D.C., 1960 (Box 22)
  - Commandery Class Reunion, 1963 (Box 22)
  - Centennial Celebration of Salina Lodge 155F and AM including speech by WB, 1964 (Box 22)
  - Grand Lodges, 1963 (Box 22)
  - Congratulatory letters and responses on election as Grand Master of Grand Encampment, 1964 (Box 22)
  - Standing Committee Reports, Fiftieth Triennial Business Sessions, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Fiftieth Triennial Corporation, 1964-1968 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence, 1966; 4 folders (Box 22)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Uniform of Grand Commanderies, 1966-1968 (Box 22)
  - Masonic cruise, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence with Paul Rodenhauser, Grand Recorder, 1968 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence with Walter A. DeLamater, Director of Knights Templar Eye Foundation, 1968 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence with John L. Crofts, Grand Master, Florida, 1968; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Correspondence, 1968; 3 folders (Box 22)
  - Miscellanea (Box 22)
  - Printed Material (Box 22)
  - Proceedings. Triennial Conclaves, 1925-1949; 1967; 10 volumes (Box 23)
- Rainbow Division
  Especially proud of his military service during World War 1, Brucker kept track of many of the men of the "Rainbow Division," maintaining a correspondence with many of them and collecting a file of their histories and narratives of their wartime activities.
  - Correspondence
    - 1919-1942 (Box 24)
    - 1959, 3 folders (Box 24)
    - 1960, 5 folders (Box 24)
    - 1961, 3 folders (Box 24)
    - 1962, 4 folders (Box 24)
    - 1963 (Box 24)
    - 1964 (Box 24)
    - 1965 (Box 24)
    - 1966 (Box 24)
    - 1967 (Box 24)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - "Diary of a Signal Platoon", 1917-1919 (Box 24)
  - List of Detroit area 32nd Division Veterans, 1934 (Box 24)
  - Joyce Kilmer Memorial, 1936 (Box 24)
  - Speeches and Reports, 1936-1962 (Box 24)
  - "Ohio Rainbow Reveille"
    - 1918-1943 (Box 24)
    - 1959-1968 (Box 24)
  - "The Observation Post", 1933-1946
    - 1933-1946 (Box 24)
    - 1959 (Box 24)
    - 1960 (Box 24)
    - 1961 (Box 24)
    - 1962 (Box 24)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 24)
    - 1968 (Box 24)
  - "Rainbow Bagpipe" (Washington, D.C.), 1959-1960 (Box 24)
  - "Rainbow Barrage" (New York), 1959-1960 (Box 24)
  - "Rainbow Reveille", 4 folders (Box 24)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Miscellanea (Box 25)
  - Annual Reunions
    - 1932-1940 (Box 25)
    - 1946-1966 (Box 25)
- Appointment books, 1933-1966
  Appointment Books date from 1933 to 1961.
  - 1933-1953, 21 volumes (Box 25)
  - 1955-1961, 7 volumes (Box 26)
  - Guest Registers, Secretary of the Army, 3 volumes (Box 26)
- Speeches, 1922-1967
  The Speeches series dates from 1922 to 1967 with the bulk of the speeches from the 1930s when Brucker was either running for office or serving as governor and in the period 1955-1960 when serving in the Eisenhower administration.
  - Speech materials
    - Peace and War, 1922-1940 (Box 27)
    - U.S. Constitution, 1923; 1939; undated (Box 27)
    - Commencement addresses, 1934-1941 (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous, 1957; undated (Box 27)
  - Texts of speeches
    - Undated, 3 folders (Box 27)
    - 1922-1926 (Box 27)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 27)
    - Concerning St. Lawrence Seaway, 1928-1932 (Box 27)
    - 1929 (Box 27)
    - 1930, 4 folders (Box 27)
    - 1931, 3 folders (Box 27)
    - 1932, 4 folders (Box 27)
    - 1933 (Box 27)
    - 1933-1934, undated concerning St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 27)
    - 1934 (Box 27)
    - 1935 (Box 27)
    - 1936, 6 folders (Box 27)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 27)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 27)
    - 1941-1942, 1946 (Box 27)
    - 1952-1957 (Box 27)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 27)
    - 1961-1967 (Box 27)
  - Political Speeches, 1958-1960; 1 volumes (Box 28)
- Secretary of the Army
  - Speeches of the Secretary of the Army (Box 28)
    [Digitized audio files are only available in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
    - 1955-1960, 6 volumes
  - Audio-tapes of Brucker speeches, November 1954-November 1960; 250 audiotapes 7-inch; reel-to-reel tapes; 2 audiotapes 10-inch; reel-to-reel tapes
    - Army Commanders Conference, November 29, 1954 (Box 29)
      (Tape 1)
    - Swearing-in of Wilber Brucker as Secretary of the Army, 1955 July 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-2-1]; mp3 file; (Swearing-in of Wilber Brucker as Secretary of the Army, Office of the Secretary of Defense, Pentagon 21 July, 1955.)
    - Civilian award to Deputy Secretary Robert Anderson, August 4, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tape 3)
    - Soo Locks Centennial, 1955 August 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-4-1]; mp3 file; (Wilber M. Brucker remarks at "Soo" Locks Centennial, Sault Ste. Marie, MI 9 August, 1955.)
    - Swearing-in of William H. Martin as Army's Director of Research and Development, September 1, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tape 5)
    - Fort Bliss Inspection, Questions and Answers, September 12-13, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tape 6)
    - Musical Salute to Reuben Robertson, Fort Leslie McNair, September 15, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tape 7)
    - "Meet the Press"; Recording of a Memorial Day Service in Japan for Korean War Dead, 1955 September 25, [Undated]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-8-1]; mp3 file; (Interview of Hon. Wilber M. Brucker on "Meet the Press" NBC program September 25, 1955. Brucker discusses budget issues in the Army, the Red Scare, nuclear weapons and the Army, and the draft.)
      - [Part 2], [85874-SR-8-2]; mp3 file; (Unknown speakers commemorating Korean War Dead in Japan)
    - Press Conference, Fort Benning, Georgia, October 21, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tape 9)
    - Association of U.S. Army, Fort Benning, Georgia, October 21, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tape 10)
    - Press Conference, Situation Room, October 26, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tapes 11-13)
    - Farewell to Major General Milburn, November 15, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tape 14)
    - Press Conference, Fort Polk, Louisiana, November 18, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tape 15)
    - Press Conference, Fort Hood, Texas, November 19, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tapes 16, 17)
    - Interview, Tokyo Airport, December 3, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tape 18)
    - Press Conference, Taipei, Taiwan, December 13, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tape 19)
    - Christmas Message, "Army Hour" broadcast, December 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tape 20)
    - Press Conference, Pentagon, December 30, 1955 (Box 29)
      (Tapes 21-23)
    - Soldiers Medal Ceremony, Pentagon, January 4, 1956 (Box 29)
      (Tape 24)
    - Patterson Award, Pentagon, February 10, 1956 (Box 29)
      (Tape 25)
    - Graduation lst RFA 55 Trainees, Cp. Chaffee, March 16, 1956 (Box 29)
      (Tape 26)
    - Irving Berlin Trophy Dedication-Pentagon, May 3, 1956 (Box 29)
      (Tape 27)
    - Armed Forces Week-Chamber of Commerce, Los Angeles, California, May 17, 1956 (Box 29)
      (Tapes 28, 29)
    - Dedication of Reserve Armory, May 17, 1956 (Box 29)
      (Tape 30)
    - Press Conference preceding Chamber of Commerce Speech, Los Angeles, California, May 17, 1956 (Box 29)
      (Tape 31)
    - Exceptional Civilian Service Award to General Sarnoff, May 23, 1956 (Box 29)
      (Tape 32)
    - Swearing-in of Governor Potter, Governor of Panama Canal, May 28, 1956 (Box 29)
      (Tape 33)
    - Economic Club of Detroit, 1956 September 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-34-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 1; Brucker discusses the threat of Communism and the Army's role in the Cold War.)
    - Economic Club of Detroit, 1956 May 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-35-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 2; Brucker discusses the threat of Communism and the Army's role in the Cold War, concludes with a story about the USS Arizona at Pearl Harbor.)
    - Bethany College Commencement, June 3, 1956 (Box 29)
      (Tapes 36, 37)
    - West Point Songs, June 1956 (Box 29)
      (Tape 38)
    - West Point Commencement, June 5, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 39)
    - Flag Day Celebration, Philadelphia, June 14, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tapes 40, 41)
    - Major Mayer (Army Med. Corps.) discusses POWs, 1956 June 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-42-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 1; Major William E. Mayer, on the medical staff at Fort Sam Houston, talks about the subject on POWs from the Korean War and their psychological health.)
    - Major Mayer (Army Medical Corps) discusses POWs, 1956 June 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-43-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 2; Major William E. Mayer, on the medical staff at Fort Sam Houston, talks about the subject on POWs from the Korean War and their psychological health.)
    - Unveiling Portrait of Secretary Stevens, June 15, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 44)
    - Swearing-in of Dr. Rollefson, Chief Scientist, June 26, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 45)
    - Officers and Men, lst Division, Fort Riley, Kansas, July 13, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 46)
    - Press Conference, Corporal Wolters, Texas, July 13, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 47)
    - Flag Ceremony, Corporal Wolters, Texas, July 13, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 48)
    - Rainbow Division Reunion, 1956 July 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-49-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 1; Rainbow Division Reunion, Dallas. Consists of a series of speeches from Rainbow Division members.)
    - Rainbow Division Reunion, 1956 July 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-50-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 2; Rainbow Division Reunion, Dallas. Consists of a series of speeches from Rainbow Division members.)
    - Rainbow Division Reunion, 1956 July 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-51-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 3; Rainbow Division Reunion, Dallas. Consists of a series of speeches from Rainbow Division members.)
    - Rainbow Division Reunion, 1956 July 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-52-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 4; Rainbow Division Reunion, Dallas. Consists of a series of speeches from Rainbow Division members.)
    - Rainbow Division Reunion, 1956 July 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-53-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 5; Rainbow Division Reunion, Dallas. Consists of a series of speeches from Rainbow Division members.)
    - Rainbow Division Reunion, 1956 July 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-54-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 6; Rainbow Division Reunion, Dallas. Consists of a series of speeches from Rainbow Division members.)
    - Rainbow Division Reunion, 1956 July 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-55-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 7; Rainbow Division Reunion, Dallas. Consists of a series of speeches from Rainbow Division members.)
    - Remarks-Navarin, France-Monument, July 21, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 56)
    - Remarks-Corporal Drum, New York USAR School, August 9, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 57)
    - Remarks-Address to 42nd Rainbow Division, Corporal Drum, August 9, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 58)
    - Certificate of Appreciation, Corporal John R. Bracken, Pentagon, August 13, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 59)
    - Press Conference, Fort Carson, Colorado, August 24, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 60)
    - American Federation of Government Employees, Willard Hotel, Washington, D.C., August 28, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 61)
    - 101st Airborne Division Reactivation, September 21, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 62)
    - Legion of Merit Presentation to Lieutenant General Antonia A. Perez, September 24, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 63)
    - Dedication of Judge Advocate School, September 26, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 64)
    - Exceptional Civilian Service Award to Henry N. Marsh, September 27, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 65)
    - St. Lawrence Seaway Luncheon, 1956 September 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-66-1]; mp3 file; (Secretary Brucker's remarks at the St. Lawrence Seaway Luncheon, Cornwall, Ontario, Canada. Commemorating the U.S. - Canada relations on the St. Lawrence Seaway.)
    - Washtenaw County Building Dedication, Ann Arbor, Michigan, September 30, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 67)
    - Swearing-in of Major General Itschner as Chief of Engineers, October 1, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 68)
    - American Ordinance Association, Aberdeen Proving Ground, Mary, October 4, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 69)
    - Presentation of Resolution to John Slezak, October 12, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 70)
    - Association of U.S. Army Meeting, October 26, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tapes 71, 72)
    - Army Times Award to Secretary Brucker, November 9, 1956 (Box 30)
      (Tape 73)
    - Dedication of Army Song and Review of Honoring Soldiers Home, 1956 November 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-74-1]; mp3 file; (Review Honoring Governor, staff and soldiers of United States Soldiers' Home including remarks by the Hon. Wilber M. Brucker, S/A and dedication of the official Army song. Fort Myer, Virginia Veteran's Day November 11, 1956. Fades out periodically - silence between 11:10 - 13:04.)
    - Washington Society of Engineers, Mayflower, November 14, 1956 (Box 31)
      (Tapes 75, 76)
    - Swearing-in of Courtney Johnson, November 16, 1956 (Box 31)
      (Tape 77)
    - Chapel of the Four Chaplains, November 18, 1956 (Box 31)
      (Tape 78)
    - Hungarian Refugees Arrival at Camp Kilmer, 1956 November 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85874-SR-79-1]; mp3 file; (Arrival of first Hungarian Refugees at Camp Kilmer, NJ. Remarks by Secretary of the Army, Wilber M. Brucker - November 19, 1956.)
    - Retired Officers Association Convention, November 30, 1956 (Box 31)
      (Tape 80)
    - U.S. Army Olympic Winners received by Secretary of Army, December 17, 1956 (Box 31)
      (Tape 81)
    - Christmas Greetings to Secretary Brucker from General Sherburne and men of the 101st Airborne Division, December 25, 1956 (Box 31)
      (Tape 82)
    - Oath of Office Administered to TAG & JAG, January 2, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 83)
    - Swearing-in of Colonel Milligan, Director of WAC, January 4, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 84)
    - Operation Understanding, Gimbels, January 14, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 85)
    - Award to Carter Burgess, January 17, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 86)
    - Harvard Club Luncheon, January 19, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 87)
    - Silver Trophy Ceremony for National Scout Representative, February 7, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 88)
    - Kiwanis Congressional Dinner, February 21, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 89)
    - George Washington Anniversary, February 22, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 90)
    - Rainbow Convention, Columbus, Ohio, February 23, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 91)
    - Award to Dr. Killian, February 26, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 92)
    - Swearing-in of Dewey Short, March 15, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 93)
    - Certificate of Achievement to Chamber of Commerce, Frederick, Md., March 21, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 94)
    - Award to Charles S. Thomas, Secretary of Navy, March 26, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 95)
    - Press Conference, Fort Mary, March 27, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 96)
    - Conference, Adjutant General Association, April 1, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 97)
    - Medal of Honor Presentation to Mrs. Page, April 2, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 98)
    - Award to Deputy Secretary of Defense Reuben Robertson, April 24, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 99)
    - Press Conference, Fort Bliss, Texas, April 26, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 100)
    - Press Conference, Chaplain's Convention, May 7, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tapes 101, 102)
    - Armed Forces Celebration Atlanta, Georgia, May 15, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 103)
    - Press Conference, Houston, Texas, May 16, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 104)
    - Air Force Day Celebration, Houston, Texas, May 16, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tapes 105, 106)
    - Chamber of Commerce Dinner, St. Louis, Missouri, May 17, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 107)
    - Dedication Reserve Training Center, St. Louis, Missouri., May 17, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tape 108)
    - Armed Forces Day Address, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, May 18, 1957 (Box 31)
      (Tapes 109, 110)
    - Stonewall Jackson Bust Dedication, New York, May 19, 1957 (Box 32)
      (Tape 111)
    - Army & Navy ROTC Awards Dinner, Detroit, Michigan, May 28, 1957 (Box 32)
      (Tape 112)
    - Association of Graduates, West Point, June 3, 1957 (Box 32)
      (Tape 113)
    - Retirement Ceremony, General Williams, June 5, 1957 (Box 32)
      (Tape 114)